A Guide to the Mutual Assurance Society of Virginia Declarations and Revaluations of Assurance, 1796-1966
Library of Virginia
- Mutual Assurance Society of Virginia Declarations and Revaluations of Assurance, 1796-1966.
  - Volume 82 [Declarations 4601-4900], 1822. (Reel MR 4131, Box b15)
    Revaluations. Cities: Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 83 [Declarations 4901-5200],1822-1823. (Reel MR 4131, Box b15)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Brownsburgh (Rockbridge), Charlestown (Jefferson), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburgh (Berkeley), Middlebrook (Augusta), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Richmond (Henrico), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Suffolk (Nansemond), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 84 [Declarations 5201-5500], 1822-1827. (Reel MR 4132, Box b16)
    New policies (#5349) and Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Belefield (Greensville), Bent Creek (Buckingham), Bernardsburg (Fluvanna), Boydton (Mecklenburg), Cartersville (Cumberland), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Columbia (Fluvanna), Fairfax (Culpeper), Falmouth (Stafford), Farmville (Prince Edward), Fincastle (Botetourt), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), James Town (Prince Edward), Jefferson (Powhatan), Lexington (Rockbridge), Madison (Madison), Manchester (Chesterfield), Milton (Albemarle), New Canton (Buckingham), Norfolk (Norfolk), (North) Milton (Albemarle), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Port Conway (King George), Port Royal (Caroline), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Standardsville (Orange), Staunton (Albemarle), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Suffolk (Nansemond), Warren (Albemarle), Warrenton (Fauquier).
  - Volume 85 [Declarations 5501-5800], 1827-1829. (Reel MR 4132, Box b16)
    Revaluations. Cities: Berryville (Frederick), Blandford (Prince George), Boydton (Mecklenburg), Centreville (Fairfax), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Dumfries (Prince William), Fairfax (Culpeper), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Front Royal (Frederick), Gosport (Norfolk, suburb of Portsmouth), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Hay Market (Prince William), Hillsborough (Loudoun), Leesburg (Loudoun), Liberty (Bedford), Lynchburg (Campbell), Martinsburgh (Berkeley), Middleburg (Loudoun), Norfolk, Occoquan (Prince William), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Petersburg suburbs (Chesterfield and Prince George), Pocahontas (Chesterfield), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Stevensburg (Frederick), Suffolk (Nansemond), Tappahannock (Essex), Urbanna (Middlesex), Washington (Culpeper), Waterford (Loudoun), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 86 [Declarations 5801-6100], 1829. (Reel MR 4132, Box b17)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Falmouth (Stafford, #6024-6036, 6038-6053), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania, #6037, 6054-6100), Martinsburg (Berkeley, #6021), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield), Williamsburg (James City, #6023). Counties: Henrico, Petersburg.
  - Volume 87 [Declarations 6101-6400],1829-1830. (Reel MR 4132, Box b17)
    Revaluations. Cities: Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania, #6101-6254), Norfolk (#6255-6400).
  - Volume 88 [Declarations 6401-6700], 1829-1830. (Reel MR 4133, Box b18)
    Revaluations. Cities: Gosport (Norfolk, suburb of Portsmouth), Norfolk, Portsmouth (Norfolk).
  - Volume 89 [Declarations 6701-7000],1829-1830. (Reel MR 4133, Box b18)
    Revaluations. Cities: Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 90 [Declarations 7001-7300],1829-1830. (Reel MR 4133, Box b19)
  - Volume 91 [Declarations 7301-7600], 1829-1830. (Reel MR 4133, Box b19)
    Revaluations. Cities: Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania, #7569-7571), Norfolk (#7572), Richmond (Henrico), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York).
  - Volume 92 [Declarations 7601-7900], 1829-1833. (Reel MR 4133, Box b20)
    Revaluations. Cities: Brownsburgh (Rockbridge), Fairfax (Culpeper), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Richmond (Henrico), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Staunton (Albemarle), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Warminister (Nelson), Waynesboro (Augusta), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York). Counties: Culpeper.
  - Volume 93 [Declarations 7901-8200], 1831-1836. (Reel MR 4134, Box b20)
    New policies. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Brownsburg (Rockbridge), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Clarksburg (Harrison), Falmouth (Stafford), Fincastle (Botetourt), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Norfolk, Orange (Orange), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Scottsville (Powhatan), Suffolk (Nansemond), Tappahannock (Essex), Waynesborough (Augusta), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 94 [Declarations 8201-8500], 1833-1836. (Reel MR 4134, Box b21)
    Revaluations. Cities: Brownsburg (Rockbridge), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Fairfax (Culpeper), Fincastle (Botetourt), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Milton (Albemarle, see North Milton), Norfolk, (North) Milton (Albemarle, see Milton), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Staunton (Augusta), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Warrenton (Fauquier), Williamsburg (James City), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 95 [Declarations 8501-8800], 1836-1841. (Reel MR 4134, Box b21)
    New policies. Cities: Buchanan (Botetourt), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Petersburg suburb (Chesterfield), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Suffolk (Nansemond), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 96 [Declarations 8801-9100], 1836. (Reel MR 4134, Box b22)
    Revaluations. Cities: Gosport (Norfolk, suburb of Portsmouth, #9087, 9090), Norfolk (Norfolk), Portsmouth (Norfolk, #9077-9086, 9091-9100).
  - Volume 97 [Declarations 9101-9400],1836-1837. (Reel MR 4134, Box b22)
    Revaluations. Cities: Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Gosport (Norfolk, suburb of Portsmouth), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Warrenton (Fauquier), Williamsburg (James City), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 98 [Declarations 9401-9700], 1836-1838. (Reel MR 4135, Box b23)
    Revaluations. Cities: Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Port Royal (Caroline), Richmond (Henrico), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Suffolk (Nansemond), Williamsburg (York).
  - Volume 99 [Declarations 9701-10000], 1836-1837. (Reel MR 4135, Box b23)
  - Volume 100 [Declarations 10001-10300], 1836-1837. (Reel MR 4135, Box b24)
  - Volume 101 [Declarations 10301-10600], 1836-1838. (Reel MR 4135, Box b24)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Manchester (Chesterfield), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield), Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 102 [Declarations 10601-10900], 1837-1838. (Reel MR 4135, Box b25)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Brownsburg (Rockbridge), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Front Royal (Warren), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield), Richmond (Henrico), Staunton (Augusta), Waynesborough (Augusta), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 103 [Declarations 10901-11200],1838-1841. (Reel MR 4136, Box b25)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Blandford (Prince George), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Charlestown (Jefferson), Dumfries (Prince William), Fincastle (Botetourt), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hay Market (Prince William), Liberty (Bedford), Lynchburg (Campbell), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Middletown (Berkeley), Milton (Albemarle, see North Milton), Norfolk, (North) Milton (Albemarle, see Milton), Occoquan (Prince William), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Warrenton (Fauquier), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 104 [Declarations 11201-11500], 1840-1843. (Reel MR 4136, Box b26)
    Revaluations. Cities: Cartersville (Cumberland), Columbia (Fluvanna), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Manchester (Chesterfield), New Canton (Buckingham), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Staunton (Augusta), Tappahannock (Essex), Urbanna (Middlesex), Williamburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 105 [Declarations 11501-11800], 1840-1845. (Reel MR 4136, Box b26)
    New policies. Cities: Alexandria, Charlottesville (Albemarle), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Liberty (Bedford), Lynchburg (Campbell), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Staunton (Augusta), Warrenton (Fauquier), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 106 [Declarations 11801-12100],1843. (Reel MR 4136, Box b27)
    Revaluations. Cities: Norfolk (#11801-12094), Portsmouth (Norfolk, #12095-12100).
  - Volume 107 [Declarations 12101-12400], 1843. (Reel MR 4137, Box b27)
    Revaluations. Cities: Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Gosport (Norfolk, suburb of Portsmouth), Portsmouth (Norfolk).
  - Volume 108 [Declarations 12401-12700], 1842-1844. (Reel MR 4137, Box b28)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince William), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Port Royal (Caroline), Richmond (Henrico), Stevensburg (Culpeper).
  - Volume 109 [Declarations 12701-13000], 1844-1845. (Reel MR 4137, Box b28)
  - Volume 110 [Declarations 13001-13300] 1844. (Reel MR 4137, Box b29)
  - Volume 111 [Declarations 13301-13600], 1844. (Reel MR 4137, Box b29)
    Revaluations. Cities: Manchester (Chesterfield, #13545-13597), Petersburg (Dinwiddie, #13598-13600), Richmond (Henrico, #13301-13544).
  - Volume 112 [Declarations 13601-13900], 1844-1845. (Reel MR 4138, Box b30)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield).
  - Volume 113 [Declarations 13901-14200], 1844-1845. (Reel MR 4138, Box b30)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Brownsburg (Rockbridge), Buchanan (Botetourt), Charlestown (Jefferson), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hillsborough (Loudoun), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Middleburg (Loudoun), Middletown (Berkeley), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Richmond (Henrico), Waterford (Loudoun), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 114 [Declarations 14201-14500], 1845-1847. (Reel MR 4138, Box b31)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Boydton (Mecklenburg), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Dumfries (Prince William), Fairfax (Culpeper), Fincastle (Botetourt), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hay Market (Prince William), Jefferson (Powhatan), Liberty (Bedford), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk, Occoquan (Prince William), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Scottsville (Powhatan), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Staunton (Augusta), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Suffolk (Nansemond), Warrenton (Fauquier), Waynesborough (Augusta), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 115 [Declarations 14501-14800], 1847-1850. (Reel MR 4138, Box b31)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Charlestown (Jefferson), Columbia (Fluvanna), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeeth City), Hicksford (Greensville), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Tappahannock (Essex), Warrenton (Fauquier), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 116 [Declarations 14801-15100], 1850. (Reel MR 4138, Box b32)
    Revaluations. Cities: Norfolk.
  - Volume 117 [Declarations 15101-15400], 1850. (Reel MR 4139, Box b32)
    Revaluations. Cities: Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Gosport (Norfolk), Norfolk, Portsmouth (Norfolk).
  - Volume 118 [Declarations 15401-15700], 1850-1851. (Reel MR 4139, Box b33)
    Revaluations. Cities: Buchanan (Botetourt), Cartersville (Cumberland), Columbia (Fluvanna), Manchester (Chesterfield), New Canton (Buckingham), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Port Royal (Caroline), Richmond (Henrico), Scottsville (Albemarle), Staunton (Augusta), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Tappahannock (Essex).
  - Volume 119 [Declarations 15701-16000], 1851. (Reel MR 4139, Box b33)
    Revaluations. Cities: Manchester (Chesterfield), Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 120 [Declarations 16001-16300], 1851. (Reel MR 4139, Box b34)
  - Volume 121 [Declarations 16301-16600], 1851. (Reel MR 4139, Box b34)
  - Volume 122 [Declarations 16601-16900],1851. (Reel MR 4140, Box b35)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George, suburb of Petersburg), Columbia (Fluvanna), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield), Richmond (Henrico, #16601-16860).
  - Volume 123 [Declarations 16901-17200], 1851. (Reel MR 4140, Box b35)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George, suburb of Petersburg), Fleets (Chesterfield, suburb of Petersburg), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield).
  - Volume 124 [Declarations 17201-17500], 1851-1852. (Reel MR 4140, Box b36)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George, suburb of Petersburg), Brownsburg (Rockbridge), Charlestown (Jefferson), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Middletown (Berkeley), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Staunton (Augusta), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 125 [Declarations 17501-17800], 1852-1854. (Reel MR 4140, Box b36)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Blandford (Prince George), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Fairfax (Culpeper), Fincastle (Botetourt), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Front Royal (Warren), Hillsborough (Loudoun), Liberty (Bedford), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Middleburg (Loudoun), Milton (Albemarle), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Richmond (Henrico), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Staunton (Augusta), Waterford (Loudoun), Waynesboro (Augusta), West End (Fairfax), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 126 [Declarations 17801-18100], 1854-1857. (Reel MR 4140, Box b37)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Madison Town (Madison), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Scottsville (Powhatan), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Staunton (Augusta).
  - Volume 127 [Declarations 18101-18400], 1857. (Reel MR 4141, Box b37)
    Revaluations. Cities: Norfolk
  - Volume 128 [Declarations 18401-18700], 1857. (Reel MR 4141, Box b38)
    Revaluations. Cities: Norfolk (#18401-18662), Portsmouth (Norfolk, #18663-18700).
  - Volume 129 [Declarations 18701-19000], 1857 (1937). (Reel MR 4141, Box b38)
    Revaluations. Cities: Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Gosport (Norfolk, suburb of Portsmouth), Hampton (Elizabeth City), New Town (Norfolk, suburb of Portsmouth), Portsmouth (Norfolk).
  - Volume 130 [Declarations 19001-19300], 1857-1858 (1931). (Reel MR 4142, Box b39)
    Revaluations. Cities: Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Manchester (Chesterfield), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Port Royal (Caroline), Norfolk, Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 131 [Declarations 19301-19600], 1858. (Reel MR 4142, Box b39)
  - Volume 132 [Declarations 19601-19900], 1858 (1905). (Reel MR 4142, Box b40)
  - Volume 133 [Declarations 19901-20200], 1858. (Reel MR 4142, Box b40)
  - Volume 134 [Declarations 20201-20500], 1858-1859. (Reel MR 4142, Box b41)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George, suburb of Petersburg), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield, suburb of Petersburg), Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 135 [Declarations 20501-20800], 1858-1859. (Reel MR 4143, Box b41)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield), Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 136 [Declarations 20801-21100], 1859-1860. (Reel MR 4143, Box b42)
    Revaluations. Cities: Brownsburg (Rockbridge), Charlestown (Jefferson), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Fredericksburg (Stafford), Hillsborough (Loudoun), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Middleburg (Loudoun), Middletown (Berkeley), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Richmond (Henrico), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Staunton (Augusta), Suffolk (Nansemond), Tappahannock (Essex), Urbanna (Middlesex), Warrenton (Fauquier), Waterford (Loudoun).
  - Volume 137 [Declarations 21101-21400], 1859-1863. (Reel MR 4143, Box b42)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Blandford (Prince George), Buchanan (Botetourt), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Culpeper Court House (Culpeper), Fincastle (Botetourt), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Liberty (Bedford), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Milton (Albemarle, see North Milton), (North) Milton (Albemarle, see Milton), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Richmond (Henrico), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 138 [Declarations 21401-21700], 1863-1867. (Reel MR 4143, Box b43)
    Revaluations. Cities: Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Lynchburg (Campbell), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 139 [Declarations 21701-22000],1867-1869. (Box b43)
  - Volume 140 [Declarations 22001-22300],1869-1872. (Box b44)
  - Volume 141 [Declarations 22301-22600],1872-1875. (Volume v141)
  - Volume 142 [Declarations 22601-22900],1875-1879. (Volume v142)
  - Volume 143 [Declarations 22901-23200],1879-1883. (Volume v143)
  - Volume 144 [Declarations 23201-23500],1883-1885. (Volume v144)
  - Volume 145 [Declarations 23501-23800],1885-1886. (Volume v145)
  - Volume 146 [Declarations 23801-24100],1887-1888. (Volume v146)
  - Volume 147 [Declarations 24101-24400],1889-1890. (Volume v147)
  - Volume 148 [Declarations 24401-24700],1890-1892. (Volume v148)
  - Volume 149 [Declarations 24701-25000],1892-1893. (Volume v149)
  - Volume 150 [Declarations 25001-25400],1893-1895. (Volume v150)
  - Volume 151 [Declarations 25401-25800],1895-1896. (Volume v151)
  - Volume 152 [Declarations 25801-26100],1896-1897. (Volume v152)
  - Volume 153 [Declarations 26101-26400],1897-1899. (Volume v153)
  - Volume 154 [Declarations 26401-26700],1899. (Volume v154)
  - Volume 155 [Declarations 26701-27000],1899-1902. (Volume v155)
  - Volume 156 [Declarations 27001-27300],1902. (Volume v156)
  - Volume 157 [Declarations 27301-27600],1903-1904. (Volume v157)
  - Volume 158 [Declarations 27601-27893 1/2],1901-1902. (Volume v158)
  - Volume 159 [Declarations 27894-28133],1903. (Volume v159)
  - Volume 160 [Declarations 28134-28433],1904-1905. (Volume v160)
  - Volume 161 [Declarations 28434-28733],1905. (Volume v161)
  - Volume 162 [Declarations 28734-29033],1906. (Volume v162)
  - Volume 163 [Declarations 29034-29333],1906. (Volume v163)
  - Volume 164 [Declarations 29334-29600],1907. (Volume v164)
  - Volume 165 [Declarations 29601-29900],1907. (Volume v165)
  - Volume 166 [Declarations 29901-30200],1908. (Volume v166)
  - Volume 167 [Declarations 30201-30500],1909. (Volume v167)
  - Volume 168 [Declarations 30501-30800],1909. (Volume v168)
  - Volume 169 [Declarations 30801-31100],1910. (Volume v169)
  - Volume 170 [Declarations 31101-31400],1910. (Volume v170)
  - Volume 171 [Declarations 31401-31700],1911. (Volume v171)
  - Volume 172 [Declarations 31701-32000],1912. (Volume v172)
  - Volume 173 [Declarations 32001-32300],1913. (Volume v173)
  - Volume 174 [Declarations 32301-32600],1913. (Volume v174)
  - Volume 175 [Declarations 32601-32900],1914. (Volume v175)
  - Volume 176 [Declarations 32901-33200],1914. (Volume v176)
  - Volume 177 [Declarations 33201-33500],1915. (Volume v177)
  - Volume 178 [Declarations 33501-33800],1916. (Volume v178)
  - Volume 179 [Declarations 33801-34100],1916. (Volume v179)
  - Volume 180 [Declarations 34101-34400],1917. (Volume v180)
  - Volume 181 [Declarations 34401-34700],1918. (Volume v181)
  - Volume 182 [Declarations 34701-35000],1919. (Volume v182)
  - Volume 183 [Declarations 35001-35300],1919. (Volume v183)
  - Volume 184 [Declarations 35301-35600],1920. (Volume v184)
  - Volume 185 [Declarations 35601-35900],1920. (Volume v185)
  - Volume 186 [Declarations 35901-36200],1921. (Volume v186)
  - Volume 187 [Declarations 36201-36500],1921. (Volume v187)
  - Volume 188 [Declarations 36501-36800],1921. (Volume v188)
  - Volume 189 [Declarations 36801-37100],1922. (Volume v189)
  - Volume 190 [Declarations 37101-37400],1922. (Volume v190)
  - Volume 191 [Declarations 37401-37700],1923. (Volume v191)
  - Volume 192 [Declarations 37701-38000],1923. (Volume v192)
  - Volume 193 [Declarations 38001-38300],1924. (Volume v193)
  - Volume 194 [Declarations 38301-38600],1924. (Volume v194)
  - Volume 195 [Declarations 38601-38900],1925. (Volume v195)
  - Volume 196 [Declarations 38901-39200],1926. (Volume v196)
  - Volume 197 [Declarations 39201-39500],1926. (Volume v197)
  - Volume 198 [Declarations 39501-39800],1927. (Volume v198)
  - Volume 199 [Declarations 39801-40100],1928. (Volume v199)
  - Volume 200 [Declarations 40101-40400],1928. (Volume v200)
  - Volume 201 [Declarations 40401-40700],1929. (Volume v201)
  - Volume 202 [Declarations 40701-41000],1930. (Volume v202)
  - Volume 203 [Declarations 41001-41300],1931. (Volume v203)
  - Volume 204 [Declarations 41301-41600],1931. (Volume v204)
  - Volume 205 [Declarations 41601-41900],1932. (Volume v205)
  - Volume 206 [Declarations 41901-42200],1933. (Volume v206)
  - Volume 207 [Declarations 42201-42500],1934. (Volume v207)
  - Volume 208 [Declarations 42501-42800],1935. (Volume v208)
  - Volume 209 [Declarations 42801-43100],1936. (Volume v209)
  - Volume 210 [Declarations 43101-43400],1937. (Volume v210)
  - Volume 211 [Declarations 43401-43700],1938. (Volume v211)
  - Volume 212 [Declarations 43701-44000],1939. (Volume v212)
  - Volume 213 [Declarations 44001-44300],1940. (Volume v213)
  - Volume 214 [Declarations 44301-44600],1941-1942. (Volume v214)
  - Volume 215 [Declarations 44601-44900],1943. (Volume v215)
  - Volume 216 [Declarations 44901-45200],1944. (Volume v216)
  - Volume 217 [Declarations 45201-45500],1945. (Volume v217)
  - Volume 218 [Declarations 45501-45800],1946. (Volume v218)
  - Volume 219 [Declarations 45801-46100],1946. (Volume v219)
  - Volume 220 [Declarations 46101-46400],1946. (Volume v220)
  - Volume 221 [Declarations 46401-46700],1946. (Volume v221)
  - Volume 222 [Declarations 46701-47000],1947. (Volume v222)
  - Volume 223 [Declarations 47001-47300],1947. (Volume v223)
  - Volume 224 [Declarations 47301-47600],1948. (Volume v224)
  - Volume 225 [Declarations 47601-47900],1948. (Volume v225)
  - Volume 226 [Declarations 47901-48200],1948. (Volume v226)
  - Volume 227 [Declarations 48201-48500],1949. (Volume v227)